[ Train Rattling ]
為什麼你不，就像是每個事實的真相，文生？
Why don't you, like,
ever realize the truth, Vince?
一個小時吃掉九的派，真是個記錄。
I ate nine pies and a meatball hero
in one hour. That's a record.
不是九個。
是八個。
It wasn't nine pies.
It was eight.
最後一盤裡你還留下兩片蘑菇。
You left two slices of mushroom
on the last tray.
懷奧萊特？
你們只吃了六個，當不了英雄。
- Violet?
- You guys, it was six pies. No hero.
我得叫醫療技術人員來把我們的胃抽出來，
半年前它已經變成三個了。
I had to call the paramedics to pumpy our stomach,
and it was three and a half years ago.
你們可否轉換話題？
When are you guys gonna talk
about something else?
當有人進門來破了紀錄，
When someone comes through
that door and breaks the record,
那我們就轉換話題。
then we'll stop talkin' about the subject.
好好享受你們的派吧！
Enjoy your pie, guys.
這是我最後一次服務了。
妳是不是忘了什麼事情？
- It's the last one I'll ever serve.
- Aren't you forgetting something?
拿開它，彼特。
我現在不想做。
Quit it, Pete.
I'm not doin' that.
這是個傳統，簽了這卡片吧。
It's a tradition.
Sign the card.
我拿到了，大夥們。
我得到了第一個簽名了。
I got it, folks.
I got the first autograph.
嘿，懷奧萊特。幹的好！
我把它釘在牆上。
- Hey, Violet. All right!
- Violet's on her way to the wall.
這是說一個住在城裡20年而離開的女孩
That's 20 years of girls leaving town.
這牆會倒楣。
我不想讓它接近那面牆。
That wall is jinxed.
I won'ts it near that wall.
希望你有比它更好的幸運。
Let's hope you have better luck
than they did.
各位先生女士。
- [CrowdShouting]
- Ladies and gentlemen.
就你們所知,我最要好的朋友, 懷奧萊特山佛德
As you all know, my best friend,
Violet Sanford,
決定--
has decided--
決定明天離開南安貝爾...
has decided to leave
South Amboy tomorrow...
旅行42公里的路程到紐約
and travel the 42 miles
to New York City.
所以--好吧，來吧。
把她帶上來，大夥們。
So-- Okay, come on.
Bring her up here, girls.
來嘛，懷奧萊特。
- Come on, Violet.
- [ Crowd Hooting ]
來嘛， 懷奧萊特。
Come on, Vi.
Come on, evetyone.
嘿，懷奧萊特,來嘛。上來這裡。
Hey, Violet, come on.
Come up here.
來嘛，寶貝。
你們這夥人！
- Come on, honey.
- You guys!
現在，我想這是今晚，也是她最後一晚
與我們同在紐澤西的聚會。
Now, I think it's only fair that tonight,
on her last night with us in Jersey,
她帶給大家一些曲子。
she grace us with a little tune.
不！
No way!
[ Girls ]
/At first I was afraid
I was petrified /
//Kept thinkin' I could never
live without you by my side//
/Then I spent so many nights
thinking how you did me wrong /
//And I grew strong
and I knew how to get along//
/ No, not I /
/ I will survive /
/ Oh, as long as
I know how to love
I know I'll be alive /
//I got all my life to live
I got all my love to give//
/ I'll survive
I will survive //
看看這!
[Man Whistles]
Lookat this!
昨晚在紐約四個人被殺了 !
Four people killed last night
in New York.
毫無理由。
No reason at all.
警方毫無線索。
Police have no leads.
[ Clicks Tongue ]
真是悲劇。
爸，你在幹嘛?
- Tragic.
- Dad, what're you doin?
我猜這是倒楣的七百萬人裡其中的四個。
I guess four out of seven million ain't so bad.
報紙頭條應該看看，
"百萬人殘存在紐約的夜晚"
Headlines should read,
"" Millions Survive Night in New York.""
爸，別說了。我知道你的意思。
吃蛋吧。
Dad, stop. I get the point.
Here. Eat your eggs.
它們不是蛋。是蛋白。
我倒寧願吃包裝紙盒。
They're not eggs. They're egg whites.
And I'd rather eat the carton.
你已經106磅了。少吃點。
不准吃速食。不准吃香腸。
You've already lost six pounds.
You're staying on this diet.
No fast food. No sausage.
喔，我買些瘦肉給你。放在冰箱裡
Oh, and I bought you some
of those Lean Cuisine meals,
and I put 'em in the freezer.
我已經流口水了。
我把你的維他命放在櫃臺上。
- My mouth is watering already.
- And I lined your vitamins up on the counter.
我不喜歡維他命。
你現在就把它吃了吧。
- I don't take vitamins.
- You do now.Just take them.
喔。我還換了電視遙控器的電池，
還設定了錄放影機的時間，所以...
Oh, and I put fresh batteries in the TV remote and
set the V.C.R. timer so--
不好意思，不好意思。
我錯過了什麼嗎？
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Am I missing something here?
我是妳老爹，你是我的孩子
跑出去獨自過活。
I'm the parent. You're the child
running away to live by herself.
我該告訴你怎麼過日子。
I should be tellin' you how to live.
好。怎麼過？
Fine. How should I live?
簡單，不要去。
[唉]
- Simple. Don't go.
- [ Sighs ]
我弄到了你最喜歡的愛爾蘭春天。
喔，還有，老爹，你什麼都可以做--
I got that Irish Spring you like.
Oh. And Dad, what every oudo--
就是不可以洗衣服。
- Don't do the laundty.
- [ Muttering ] Don't do the laundty.
讓乾洗的人弄，我每星期天回來也會弄。
Just leave it by the dtyer and I'll
do it when I come home evety Sunday.
呵,真有趣。
Ah, this is interesting.
他們說地鐵的扶手有一天會斷的。
They say the handrails
on the subway system could one day
lead to an outbreak of plague.
老爹，看這。
Dad. Look.
你說我要當什麼都可以。
You said I could be
whatever I wanna be.
除了到紐約當歌手之外。
I never said songwriter in New York City.
That's the exception.
你什麼都說了，我也相信你，所以--
You said anything,
and I believed you, so--
沒有你的支持我也不會離開家的。
[ Sighs ] I'm not leavin' this house
without your support.
那是葛絡莉亞，快點，那將是什麼？
- [CarHorn Honking]
- That's Gloria. What's it gonna be?
唉
[ Sighs ]
懷奧萊特，我見過當你媽沒有做到它
的那時候有多麼的辛苦。
Violet, I saw how hard it was
for your mother when she didn't make it.
但是她如果還在這，她會叫我閉嘴。
But if she was here,
she'd tell me to shutup,
給妳祝福以及一個大力的擁抱。
wish you luck and give you a big hug.
我不會給妳大力一抱，
也不給妳祝福，但...
I'm not gonna give you a big hug,
and I'm not gonna wish you luck, but...
我會跟我的咖啡一起坐在這，
閉嘴，還有裝傻。
I am gonna shut up, sit here
with my coffee and pretend to be mad.
這樣可以嗎？
Is that okay?
這是最後一籃了。
This is the last of it.
寶貝，你還可以吧？
行，沒問題。
- Honey, are you okay with that?
- Yeah, I got it.
沒問題。等一下。
I got it. Wait.
好了。所有東西都好了。
All right.
That's everything.
抱抱吧。祝你好運。
- Let's hit it.
- Good luck.
就像我所說的。
There, I said it.
我愛你。
若你不肯定的話，
- Love you.
- Put some pepper spray in your
purse. Even if you're not sure.
就明說吧。
Just start spraying.
你知道的，你並不孤單，山佛德先生
You know, you're not alone,
Mr. Sanford.
嘿，也許你我有時候該共進晚餐的。
Hey, you know, me and you
should have dinner sometime.
我要把門鎖上了。
I'm lockin' the doors.
//At first I was afraid
I was petrified//
//Kept thinkin' I could never
live without you by my side//
// Oh, no, not I//
//I will survive//
//As long as I have love to give
I know I'll bealive//
//I've got all my life to live
I've got all my love to give//
//I will survive//
//I will survive////
太好了，就是這了。
All right.
This is it.
你認為如何？
What do you think?
我想你應該需要這個。
I had a feeling
you were gonna need this.
你在幹嘛啊？
什麼？不過就是我存下來的急用現金罷了。
- What are you doing?
- What? It's just some
emergency cash I saved up.
寶貝，看看這個地方，
這就是我所說的緊急情況。
Honey, from the looks of this place,
I'd say this is our emergency.
嗯，我不會拿的。
Well, I'm not takin' it.
好吧，那麼，
Fine, then.
這是放在你冰箱裡的財物了。
I'm freezing your assets.
那麼，謝謝你。
So, thanks for evetything.
我會再打電話給妳的。
- I'll call ya.
- [ Sniffing ]
怎麼了？
What is this?
我們生活中，你我常說的同一樣東西。
It's just that all our lives,
you know, we always had one thing
in common, you and me.
你在說什麼啊？
What are you talking about?
你知道我說的，
我們不會失去我們的童貞...
It's like, you know we said
we wouldn't lose our virginity...
直到我們結婚前那是不會發生的。
until we got married,
and that didn't happen.
然後說在我們上大學或短期大學...
And then we said we'd go to
college or junior college...
或是牙醫學校，你知道的，
or dental hygienist school,
you know.
但還是連一次也沒有。
And that didn't happen.
我們不曾貫徹過一件事情，你知道的。
We've never followed through
on a single thing, you know.
我想那是令我們那麼特別的原因。
And I think that's
what makes us so special.
這就是妳哭的原因？
[ Chuckles ]
And this is why you're crying?
這個...
Well...
很久以前你就告訴我說你要搬去紐約。
a long time ago you told me
that you were gonna move to New York.
但每個人都認為你會待在紐澤西並結婚
就像我跟丹尼那樣。
But evetyone thought you'd just
stay in Jersey and get married
like me and Danny are gonna.
你知道的，看看你，
You know. And-- And look at you.
無論如何，你做的都是對的，
No matter what,
you really did it right,
我都一直以你為榮。
and I'm so proud of you.
唉
[ Sighs ]
// [ Soft Ballad ]
夠了！妳聽到了嗎？
[Pounding]
Enough! You hear me?
安靜點！夠了！
[Shouting]
You be quiet! Enough in there!
/ I don't like to be
alone in the night /
/And I don't like to
hear I'm wrong when I'm right /
/And I don't like to /
/ Have the rain on my shoe //
嗨，我是懷奧萊特山佛德。
我剛搬來紐約。
Hi. I'm Violet Sanford.
I just recently moved to New York,
不知道你可否把我的帶子給你們
其中一個歌手。
and I was wondering
if you would give my tape
to one of your artists.
懷奧萊特，好可愛喔。
Violet, that is so cute.
現在讓我告訴你我是誰。
我叫溫蒂，我第一次搬來紐約時...
Now, let me tell you about me.
My name is Wendy,
and I first moved to New York...
才21歲，想當個舞蹈家，但是沒成功。
when I was 21 to be a dancer,
but I broke my big toe.
然後我被這甩了我的混蛋喚醒去
加入和平工作團。
And then I got knocked up
by this actor who dumped me
to join the Peace Corps.
過去16年來我獨自扶養我女兒。
So for the last 16 years
I been raisin' my daughter
all by myself.
兩週前她告訴我她是個雙性戀者...
And then two weeks ago
she tells me that she is a bisexual...
她在這星球上最討厭我不過了。
and that she hates me more
than any person on this planet.
[Chuckles]
那麼，告訴我怎麼幫助你。
Now, tell me how I can
help you, please,
因為我渴望死要讓你美夢成真。
because I am dying
to make your dreams come true.
你不能拿這帶子除非它來自於一代理商。
You don't take the tape
unless it comes from an agent,
但是我還沒發行哪來的代理商啊？
but I can't get an agent
until I get published?
如果我們聽了你的帶子，
你也不會獲得任何...
If we were to listen to that tape,
that would give you grounds...
版權或是剽竊的訴訟案件。
for a copyright
or plagiarism law suit.
這不過是捲帶子，
我所想要的只不過是有人能夠唱我的歌。
It's just a little tape.
All I want is someone to sing my songs.
歡迎加入音樂行業。
Welcome to the music business.
鈴...
[Phone Ringing]
晚安，請出示ID卡。
嗨，喔，好的。
- Good evening. I.D., please.
- Hi. Uh, sure.
/ Maybe /
//Finda way tomakeit
back someday//
要喝什麼？
我問你些事情。
- What can I get you?
- Let me ask you something.
我是寫歌的，這裡有人可以
跟我談談我寫的歌嗎？
I'm a songwriter. Is there someone
here I could talk to about my songs?
我在這當撒克斯風手掙扎了12年
I've been a struggling sax player for 12 years.
你要什麼？
百事可樂跟脆餅。
- What can I get you from the bar?
- Pepsi and some crackers.
////[Continues]
嘿，你好嗎？
- [ People Chattering ]
- Hey. How are you doing?
/Then I hope there's someone
out there /
對不起，那傢伙是誰？
Excuse me.
Who's that guy?
那應該是歐當奴先生。
That would be Mr. O'Donnell.
歐當奴先生。
他是個經紀人之類的嗎？
Mr. O'Donnell.
He's the manager or something?
是的，他是個經紀人。
他負責發掘樂團和...
Yeah. He's the music manager.
He's in charge of finding bands and...
代理新的藝人。
booking new talent.
//Run away with myheart//
//Run away with myhope////
嘿，歐當奴，你死去哪了？
Hey, where the hell were you,
O'Donnell?
我這有15個訂位的客人卻沒人有燒烤。
I got 15 orders stacked up here
and nobody to run the grill.
全部15份嗎，華特？
Fifteen orders, Walt.
Is that all?
給我10分鐘，我會趕上的。
休息一下吧。
Gimme ten minutes,
I'll catch us up. Go on. Lie down.
輕鬆點，你看起來累了。
Relax. You look tired.
我們可以晚點再談加薪的事情。
We can talk about my raise later.
你以為這裡是澳洲？
沒得加薪，我要把你炒魷魚。
You think this is Australia?
There's no raise. I'm about to fire you.
[DoorOpens, People Laughing]
啊，抱歉，歐當奴先生嗎？
Um, excuse me.
Mr. O'Donnell?
是的。
歐當奴先生，我是懷奧萊特山佛德。
- Yes.
- Mr. O'Donnell.
My name is Violet Sanford.
我是個寫歌的，我想把這個給你。
I'm a songwriter.
I just wanted to give this to you.
我知道這不是一般專業呈交帶子的方式，
I know it's not the most professional
way to submit a tape.
但這對我從未有過。
我也是。
- But this is all pretty new to me.
- It's pretty new to me too.
像你這樣一個俱樂部的經理，
你應該知道東岸每一個樂團吧。
I just figured as the manager
of a club like this, you must know
every band on the East Coast.
經理...這家俱樂部。
The manager...
of this club.
嗯--
Um--
你們先走吧，我待會兒會趕上。
好的。
- You guys go ahead. I'll catch up.
- Sure thing.
歐當奴先生。
Mr. O'Donnell.
[ Clears Throat ]
我通常不這麼做，懷奧萊特。
I don't usually do this,Violet.
嗯，但我--我對你有些感覺。
Um, but I-- I have a feeling about you.
我就拿了這帶子看看能怎麼辦。
謝謝你。
- So I'm gonna take your tape,
and I'm gonna see what I can do.
- Thankyou.
我真不敢相信這有多麼容易。
I can't believe how easy this was.
我也是。
Neither can I.
嗯，想喝杯咖啡或其他之類的嗎？
Uh, you wanna go for some coffee or something?
歐當奴，我看起來如何啊？
天殺的處女？
O'Donnell, who do I look like?
Your god damn maid?
那是歐當奴先生，
That's Mr. O'Donnell,
但這次就算了。
but I'll let it slide this time.
我早告訴過你把這爛東西帶回家去洗。
I told you to take your stuff home and wash it.
你這前面牛油都黏成塊了。
You got cow grease caked on the front.
華特，我要警告你的態度--你被炒魷魚了。
Walt, I've warned you about your attitude--
You're fired.
喔，小子，你最好不要逼我。
Oh, you better not push me, kid.
我可以找到一百個其他像你一樣
能做火雞漢堡的小鬼。
I can find a hundred other little punks like you,
can burn a turkey burger.
廉價工資的小鬼。
Minimum wage punk.
不介意我們重來一遍吧。啊...
Maybe we should start over. Uh...
我是凱文歐當奴，
I'm Kevin O'Donnell,
我在這家斐濟美人魚燒烤店工作。
and I work the grill here at the
Fiji Mermaid Club.
我剛把自己像個呆子一樣耍了。
I just made a complete fool of myself.
我要告訴你，
I was gonna tell you.
我幾乎確定剛才是在跟你說話。
I'm almost sure I would have told you.
我要你知道我不是在跟著妳回家，
I just want you to know
I'm not following you home.
不過是走在有26區遠的錯誤方向
I'm just walking myself 26
blocks in the wrong direction.
請你離開我。
我剛沒提到我有多麼抱歉嗎？
- I asked you to leave me alone.
- Did I mention how sorry I am?
我是指那不全是我的錯。
剛是妳自己來找我的。
I mean, not that it's all my fault.
You did throw yourself at me.
我才沒有。
I didn't throw myself at you.
我是裝可愛天真所以請你饒了我吧。
I was pretending to be sweet
and innocent so you'd give me a break.
我可以問你個問題嗎？
什麼？
- Can I ask you a question?
- What?
你能給的理由說明為何我們在兜圈走？
你迷路了嗎？
Is there a reason we just walked
in a circle? Are you lost?
我沒迷路。
有人把我的路移動了。
I'm not lost.
Somebody just moved my street.
你--你要來玩嗎？
You-- You wanna play a game?
我打賭我可以猜出你從哪來。
I bet I can guess where you're from.
我要說出我的答案。
I'm about to get out my pepper spray.
我認為你是從大城市來的。
I reckon you're from a big city.
沒有這裡的耳環的標誌...
And there's no sign from here
of a belly button ring...
或是尖銳的口音。
or a tongue piercing.
我猜芝加哥。
好吧。
- I gotta go with Chicago.
- Okay.
我從不讓人盯在我屁股後面
所以我要說晚安了。
I've never had anyone stare
at my ass for half an hour,
so I'm gonna say good night.
希望你也會說。
And I'm hoping you're gonna say it back.
好吧，我知道了。
Okay. I can take a hint.
我真的認識很多在音樂界裡的人。
I really do know a lot of people
in the music business.
你就是不會放棄，是吧？
You just don't give up,
doya?
嗯，這可不是可愛天真的事。真的。
晚安，凱文。
- Well, it was the sweet and
innocent thing. It did me in.
- Good night, Kevin.
正確來說，我只有前面15分鐘
是盯著你的屁股看。
Just for the record,
I was only staring at your ass
for the first 15 minutes.
威廉莫理斯，我不是有意思要打擾。
-[Man Answering Phone]
William Morris.
- I don't mean to interrupt.
我只不過是想要留下這個。
我會傳達的。
- I just want to leave this--
- I'll transfer.
威廉莫理斯，請留下它。
是個試音帶，我是個寫歌的。
- William Morris. Please hold.
- It's a demo. I'm a song writer.
威廉莫理斯，我會一直在這的。
William Morris.
I'll be right with you.
[ Phones Disconnect ]
我只不過想把這留給惠妮跟瑪麗亞。
I just want to leave this
for Whitney and Mariah.
我確定他們是你的朋友。
聽好，
- I'm sure they're personal friends of yours.
- Look.
我想它在你的浴室裡聽起來很棒，
但是卡拉OK半小時前結束。
I'm sure it sounds great in your shower,
but karaoke ended a half hour ago.
所以如果你想要讓你的歌被聽到，
你必須帶著它們...
So if you'd like to get your songs heard,
you're gonna have to take them...
像其他每一個人到公開的駐唱吧台去。
to an open mic night
just like everyone else.
威廉莫理斯。
[ Phones Resume Ringing ]
William Morris.
我會轉達的。
你還沒有被批准喔。
I'll transfer.
You're not getting validated.
// Caughtin amirror//
-[PoolBalls Clacking]
- / Looking through
sympathetic eyes /
需要什麼嗎？
嗯--
- Can I help you?
- Um--
是的，嗨，嗯，我想你們今晚
所有地方都會被擠滿，
Yeah, hi. Uh, I'm sure all your spaces
are filled for tonight.
我只是想下來看看這個公開的駐唱吧台。
I just wanted to come down
and check out what this whole
open mic thing was about.
我可以擠出10分鐘給妳，
有兩三個經常駐唱的打電話來說生病了。
I can squeeze you in in ten minutes.
A couple of my regulars, they called in sick.
所以，嗯，我還有些地方可填。
So, uh, I've got some spaces to fill.
在這簽名還有自己好好準備吧。
I need you to sign your name
in here and get yourself ready.
////[Singer Continues]
廁所在角落如果你想要吐的話。
Bathroom's around the corner
if you want to throw up.
下一位是位叫做懷奧萊特山佛德
的年輕小姐
Next up we have a young lady
named Violet Sanford.
那麼我們一起鼓掌歡迎來自紐澤西的
懷奧萊特山佛德。上來吧，懷奧萊特。
So let's put our hands together for NewJersey's
own Violet Sanford! Come on up, Violet.
很好！開始吧。
耶，哇！
Good! There we go.
Yeah. Whoo!
耶，懷奧萊特！
-[Woman] Yea, Violet!
-[ScatteredApplause, Whistles]
喔喔。
Oh, oops.
我有點緊張。
我們也是，寶貝。
- I'm a little nervous.
- So are we, honey.
別逗我們了，寶貝！
唱吧！
Don't tease me, honey!
Sing!
饒了她吧。
[Man #@]
Come on, give her a break.
我很抱歉。
I'm sorry.
哈羅？
Hello?
[ Crying ]
你必須提起勁來！
你看起來像是你的狗被人碾過一樣。
You gotta cheer up. You look like
somebody ran over your dog.
嘿，嗯，這一片餡餅多少？
Hey, um, how much is a slice of pie?
喔，嗯，
Oh, uh,
我們碰巧有全鎮最棒的法國蘋果派，
we happen to have
the best French apple in town.
嗯，店長請客。
And, uh, it's on the house.
閉嘴。
你注意點。
-Shut up.
- You just have to pay attention.
行嗎？
20塊。
- Okay?
- Twenty.
20塊說它是個漂亮女人。
我再加10塊。
- Twenty says it's Pretty Woman.
- I will raise you ten,
因為它是孤獨的。
because it is Home Alone.
喔？
你們大家必須讀這標題，
- Oh?
- You guys have to read the signs.
我做它做是搶救雷恩大兵。
I call with Saving Private Ryan.
什麼？讓我們跳過，
還有來自奧斯汀的珍妮佛小姐...
- What?
- Let's fip this over, and Miss Jennifer from Austin...
說她最喜歡的電影是--
says her
favorite movie is--
不可能，不可能的！
你早看過這個了！
No way. There's no way!
You already saw this one.
喔，你真是作弊的傢伙。
Oh, you are such a cheater.
哈囉。一個裸體的女孩在陸軍靴裡？
簡單。
Hello. A naked girl in army boots?
Easy play to call.
謝謝。
這些靴子看起來好可愛。
- Thank you.
- Those boots are kinda cute.
我必須買些來。
- I have to get me some of those.
- [ Chuckles ]
等一下，等一下，等一下，羅蜜歐。
你把它調大聲點，寶貝。那是改奏的即興爵士。
Wait, wait, wait. Oh, Romero.
You gotta turn that up, baby. That is the jam.
調大聲點！
喔,不。
- Turn it up!
There you go, there you go.
- Oh, no.
你在幹嘛啊？
記得這個嗎？記個這個嗎？
- Girl, what are you doing?
- Remember this? Remember this?
肚皮舞。
- [Girls Groaning]
- Belly dancing.
[ Hooting ]
你認識她們嗎？
喔，是的，她們每天早上大概這時候來。
- Do you know those girls?
- Oh, yeah. They're here every
morning around this time.
解脫自己。
等一下，等一下。
- Winding down.
- Wait, wait.
她們必須如此，因為她們工作的關係。
妓女嗎？
- They have to, in their line of work.
- Are they hookers?
不。
No.
女狼。
Coyotes.
好吧。
[ Laughs ]
All right.
你們大家想看艾爾在我生日給我什麼嗎？
You guys? You guys wanna see
what Al gave me for my birthday?
這個。
你讓他烙印在你身上？
- This.
- You let him brand you?
不可愛嗎？
她讓他們烙印在她身上。
- Isn't it cute?
- She let them an brand her.
嘿，看看這個，小姐們。
我們每一個今晚賺了300塊錢。
Hey, check it out, ladies.
We each made 300 bucks tonight.
嗯--     你們確定還要上法律學院嗎？
- Mmm.
- You sure you wanna be
goin' off to law school?
嗯？
Hmm?
讓我們乾杯吧。
耶。
- Let's make a toast.
- Yeah.
慶祝佐伊上週成為女狼的一員。
To Zoe's last week as a Coyote.
喔。
她是不可能回原位了。
- Oh.
- She's gonna be impossible to replace.
我想告訴你們我永遠也不會忘記你們的。
I just wanna tell you both
that I will never, ever forget you.
誰啊？
[Woman]
Who's up there?
我想找店長。
嘿，下來吧。順便帶一箱下來。
- I'm lookin' for the owner.
- Hey, come on down.
Bring a case with you.
你在這幹嘛？
What are you doin' here?
嗯，我想把這箱子放下，你要我放哪啊？
看情況，你要幹嘛啊？
- Uh, I'm gonna drop this case. Where do you want me to put it?
- That depends. What doya want?
嗯，我聽說你這也許需要另招新人，嗯--
Well, I heard you might need
anew, uh--
喔，那件事喔，也許有個空的職缺，
That, uh, there might be a job opening.
放到那邊，讓我看看，
Put it right there.
Let me take a look atya.
讓我猜猜，
[ Groans ]
Let me guess.
皮德特蒙區，北達科他州
Piedmont, North Dakota.
南安貝爾，紐澤西。
South Amboy, NewJersey.
一樣的啦。你有嗑藥嗎？
Same thing.
You do any drugs?
咖啡就好，那是我目前所能負擔的起的。
Just coffee.
That's all I can afford right now.
我看看你的手臂。
當真？
- Let me see your arms.
- Are you kidding?
我看起來像嗎？
Do I  look like I'm kidding?
喔，你手上這疤怎麼搞的？
Ooh, where'd you get
that scar on your wrist?
四年前被披薩烤箱燙到的。
Pizza oven. It's a permanent
burn from pulling slices for four years.
那真是我所過最叫人難過的事了。
That could be the saddest thing
I've ever heard.
嗯，那接下來咧？尿液檢體？
哈哈∼
- Um, what's next?
You want a urine sample?
- Ha, ha.
我比較喜歡血液的。
I prefer blood.
那麼，你真的是店長嗎？
因為我這幾天過的蠻糟的，
Look, are you really the owner?
'Cause I've had a rough couple of days,
最後還被些女侍浪費我的時間。
and so the last thing I need is some waitress
on a power trip wastin' my time.
你星期五開始吧，11點鐘到那。
那時是我們要開始忙的時候。
You start Friday night. Be there at 11 :00.
That's when we get busy.
你要給我工作？
我要給妳個試音的機會。
- You're givin' me a job?
- I'm givin' you an audition.
不要遲到囉，紐澤西的女孩。
Don't be late,Jersey girl.
我不是想碰運氣的，但我可以問為何你要用我？
I don't mean to press my luck,but would you
mind telling me why you're hiring me?
因為一般的男人...
Because the average male...
四處晃盪像是褲子裡有個學走路的小孩似的，
is walking around with a toddler
inside of his pants.
一個兩歲大的傢伙在他的"碼頭"裡。
A two year old, right there
inside his Dockers.
男人的褲子裡有兩歲大的孩子？
那就是你雇用我的原因？
Men have two-year-old children in their pants?
That's why you're hiring me?
你像是個幼稚園老師，孩子都喜歡的那種。
You look like a kindergarten teacher.
The kids'll love it.
真抱歉我問這個。
Sorry I asked.
請出示ID卡。
I.D., please.
喔，我是今晚來這上班的。
Oh. I'm supposed to
start work here tonight.
直接進去吧。嘿，你開始就有個不錯的晚上喔。
Go ahead. Hey, you picked a good night to start.
現在這有點擠，但待會兒就會恢復。
好的。
- It's a little slow right now, but it should pick up.
- Okay.
//Love is like a bomb
Baby, come on get it on//
-//Livin' like a lover
with a radar phone//
- [ Screams ]
//Lookin' like a tramp
Like a video vamp//
//Demolition woman
Can I bey our man//
這酒吧裡是有個教會聚會嗎？
來點噪音吧！
Is this a church meeting
or is this a bar? Make some noise!
[ Whooping, Shouting ]
好耶！
- Yeah!
-// Come on//
想要嗎？
- Want it?
-// Take a bottle//
//Shake it up//
//Break the bubble//
//Break it up//
//Pour some sugar on me//
// Ooh, in the name of love//
//Poor some sugar on me//
// Come on, fire me up//
抱歉，真的對不起。
-//Pour your sugar on me//
- I'm sorry. Sorry!
我可不這麼認為。
時間剛剛好，
- I don't think so.
-Just in time.
你要去哪啊？
嗯，我正要--我正想說找你。
- Where you goin'?
- Uh, I was-- I was looking for you.
很好，走吧。
Good. Let's go.
//
//Listen, red light, yellow
light, green light, go//
// Crazy little woman
in a one-man show//
//Mirror queen, mannequin
rhythm of love//
蠻喜歡你的精彩部分。
謝謝。
- Really love your top.
- Thanks.
有了，嗯，來點賣點--
- I got it, um, on sale--
-//Loosen up, uh, loosen up//
// You gotta squeeze a little
squeeze a little
tease a little more//
好了。頭髮。
Okay. Hair.
看你的了！
- Let's see your moves.
- [ Hoots ]
那是瑞秋，你可以從她學到很多。
That's Rachel. You can learn a lot from her.
她剛剪了一些人一小撮頭髮。
She just cut some guy's pony tail off.
是的。那些求歡的客人還要求
她開些情緒管理課程...
Yeah. The court ordered her
to take anger management classes...
之後她還痛打一位抓她屁股的客人。
after she pummeled a customer
for grabbin' her ass.
那是他要尋求些快感刺激。
我給了她加薪。慢用。
- [ Whooping ]
- He pressed charges. I gave her a raise. Cheers.
//Pour some sugar on me//
這只有兩條規矩，行嗎？
你要什麼？  兩瓶啤酒。
- There is only two rules, okay? What do you want?
- Two beers.
不要跟客人約會。
好的。
- Don't date the customers.
- Okay.
第二條，絕對不要帶你的男朋友來這。
Second, don't ever bring
your boyfriends into my bar.
在這妳要顯得可以被泡，但是又不能被泡。
As of this moment you are to appear available,
but never be available.
違反規定，當場就把妳開除。
Break my rules, I fire you on the spot.
我--我了解了。
天啊。
- I-- I understand.
-Jesus.
嘿！嘿，所有的人！
Hey! Hey, everybody!
閉嘴！
Shut up!
我要向你們介紹我們的新來的妞...
I'd like you to meet my new girl...
她的名字是--
懷奧萊特。
- whose name is--
- Violet.
杰西。
Jersey.
杰西是位前任的幼稚園老師...
- [ Cheering ]
-Jersey is an ex-kindergarten teacher...
以前是位逃離修道院的修女...
and a former nun who just escaped
from the convent...
並且厭煩當個紐約市裡的唯一一個處女。
and is tired of being the only virgin
in New York City.
有沒有人請她喝杯飲料啊？嗚哇！
Would anyone like to buy her a drink? Whoa!
拜託，動動吧！妳在這上班咧。
抱歉。
- Come on, move! I'm workin' here.
- Sorry.
四份加蘇打水的瑪格列特。
好的。
- Four margaritas with salt.
- All right.
龍舌蘭酒。
不要混其它的酒，不加蘇打水，不要摻任何東西。
Got tequila.
No mix, no salt, no blender.
好的，來份黑色俄羅斯如何？
加伏特加，不要咖啡酒。
- Okay, how about a black Russian?
- Got vodka, no Kahlua.
白酒。
純的。
- White wine.
- Never carry the stuff.
那麼基本上你有--
Jim,Jack,Johnny Red,Johnny Black 還有 Jose
- So basically you have--
-Jim,Jack,Johnny Red,Johnny Black and Jose.
都是我最喜歡的。你可以挑你喜歡的。
All my favorite men. You can have it anyway
you like, as long as it's in a shot glass.
好吧，我要啤酒。
Okay, I'll take a beer.
四塊錢。
我是康妮，俄羅斯的傢伙。
- Four dollars.
- I'm Cammie, the Russian tease.
懷奧萊特，紐澤西的修女。
Violet, the Jersey nun.
那一個是瑞秋，紐約的賤人。
That one's Rachel, the New York bitch.
我們都扮演我們的角色，
只有瑞秋是真正的賤人。
We all play our little parts,
only Rachel really is a bitch.
還有我是真正的喜歡整人。
And I really am a tease.
康妮，如果你不到處睡的話，
你就不會是那樣了。
Cammie, you can only be a tease
if you stop sleepin' around, babe.
是喔，我會一直忘記那部分的。
Yeah. I keep forgetting that part.
我要一份龍舌蘭酒，
不要忘了也給你這小可愛一份。
I'll have a shot of tequila, and don't
forget one for your pretty little self.
喔，謝謝，但自從我因喝過那酒而真正
醉過一次後，我再也不碰那東西了。
Oh, thanks, but ever since I got really drunk
on tequila, I never drink the stuff anymore.
嘿，莉兒！你的新來的妞正在替你
婉拒真正的好酒。
Hey, Lil! Your new girl's refusing
your good booze.
不是！我--我正建議這位男士
請我一份雙份的。
No! I was-- I was suggesting
this gentleman buy me a double.
這還比較像樣。
That's more like it.
哦！
我要八種。
- Whoa!
- I need eight shots.
四份加拿大威士忌，四份 South of the Border，
six-pack MGD 還有一份雙份的 blended back。
Four Canadian, four South of the Border,
six-pack MGD and a double-blended back.
你要八種什麼？
我知道了。
- You want eight shots of what?
- I got it.
寶貝，四六比。
Forty-six even, honey.
嘿，莉兒！呦！
Hey, Lil! Yo!
你新來的紐澤西妞手腳趕不上啊。
Your Jersey girl can't quite keep up.
嘿，給我份蘇格蘭威士忌跟水。
Hey, gimme a Scotch and water.
好的，就依你。
莉兒，我們賣的威士忌有附水嗎？
- Okay, you got it.
- Lil, do we serve water with our whiskey?
我們這不賣的！
Only water I serve's got barley and hops in it!
嘿，你們大家！
我們這吧有賣水嗎？
Hey, everybody!
Do we serve water in this bar?
哦！不要水！不要水！
[ Crowd Chanting ]
Hell, no. H2O! Hell, no. H2O!
不要水！
[ Chanting Continues ]
Hell no, H2O!
[ Hooting ]
是時候了，杰西。一起來吧！
Sink or swim time, Jersey.
Get up there!
// The devil's in the house
of the rising sun//
我不會跳這種舞。
I can't do that dance.
// Granny, does your dog bite
No, child, no//
好吧。
Okay.
//
這有些現金，就修女而言你表現還不錯。
你要炒我魷魚？
- Here's some cash. You did okay for a nun.
- You're firing me?
我早告訴過你這不是試演的地方。
I told you this was an audition.
謝謝你來這兒，離開吧！
Thanks for comin'in.
Now, get outta here.
//Johnny said
Devil,just come on back
if you ever wanna try again//
//I done told you once
you son of abitch, I'm the
best there's ever been//
//He played fire on them ountain
Run, boy, run//
//Devil's in the house
of the risin'sun//
住手！
Please!
嘿！
-// Chicken in the bread pan
pickin' out dough//
- Hey!
兩位，兩位，退後點，分開！
Guys, guys, back off,
back off!.
聽好，你們只有兩種選擇，
Look, the way I see it,
you got two choices.
一是繼續打把自己弄得血淋淋的，
You can start a fight here,
throw some punches, get a bloody
nose, make fools of yourselves,
或是這10元...
or you can take this ten bucks
I got right here...
請那吧台旁兩位美麗的小姐喝酒。
and buy these two pretty ladies
a round at the bar.
怎樣，如何？
去吧台那吧！
- Come on. What do you say?
- Let's go to the bar!
舞會時間！
Party!
慢點，杰西，我很想知道那是哪來的。
-////[Continues]
- Hold it,Jersey.
I'm just dyin' to know where that came from.
試著在11月的星期一晚上當巨人們玩著
牛仔的遊戲時在旁招呼酒或披薩。
Try serving a beer and pizza on Monday nights
when the Giants play the Cowboys in November.
我給妳第二次機會。
I'm giving you a second audition.
那邊街角有間店，明天中午到那報到。
There's a store at the corner of Sixth and Hill.
Be there at noon tomorrow.
我會派我的流行服飾顧問帶你去購物的。
I'm sending my fashion coordinator there
to take you shopping.
現在在我改變心意前回家去吧。
Now go home before I change my mind.
嘿，還有，杰西，如果另一個晚上
你能活下來的話，我會很訝異的。
Hey, and Jersey. I'd be shocked
if you survive another night.
// Granny, will your dog bite
No, child, no////
繼續來吧！
Here we go!
左腳，右腳，踢踏，踢踏，踢踏。
And left, and right,
clog, clog, clog.
//
喔，耶！
Oh, yeah!
那麼，嗯，告訴我多一點有關這個酒吧的事。
So, uh, tell me more about this bar.
那到底是個什麼地方？
我不知道，就是個酒吧，爸。
- What kind of place is it?
- I don't know. It's just a bar, Dad.
沒什麼大不了的。
你在吃什麼？
It's no big deal.
What are you eating?
一種烹飪餐點，有飯跟菜，蠻好吃的。
One of those Lean Cuisine meals.
Rice and vegetables. Delicious.
喔！看吧，它們是很好的，沒錯吧？
嗯。
- Oh! See, they're good. Right?
- Mmm. Yum.
對了，你的歌寫的怎麼樣了？
So, well, what's going on
with your song writing?
喔！寫的歌啊，他還拿了我的帶子。
Song writing. Oh!
He still has my tape.
//Dance, dance, dance//
//Dance////
我要我的帶子。
I want my tape.
我就知道你會回來找我。
-////[Continues]
- I had a feeling you'd be back to see me.
在廚房不准約會，歐當奴。
我不會待在這的。
- No dates in the kitchen, O'Donnell.
- I'm not staying.
我--我只是要我的帶子。
I-- I just want my tape.
麻煩你。
Please.
謝謝，再見。
這歌全都是妳寫的嗎？
- Thanks. Bye.
- Did you really write all those songs?
你聽了我的帶子？
You listened to my tape?
不，當然沒有。
我的意思是，那像是侵犯別人的隱私一樣。
No, of course not.
I mean, that would be invasion of privacy.
/ Baby, you're the right kind
of love //
繼續笑啊，因為不管你說什麼都
無法困擾我的。
Go ahead, laugh it up.'Cause there's nothing
you can say that's gonna bother me.
我只是試著要告訴你我喜歡你的音樂。
I'm just trying to tell you I like your music.
我是指，你常會接受別人的讚美嗎？
I mean, do you always take compliments so well?
我要走了。
等等！嗯--
- I gotta go.
- Wait! Uh--
我想再見到你，你在哪上班啊？
I wanna see you again.
Where are you workin'?
我是個女狼。
很好。
- I'm a Coyote.
- [ Howls ]
- Good.
那是什麼鬼東西啊？
如果你想要再見到我的話，自個兒想辦法吧。
- And what the hell is that?
- If you want to see me again, you'll figure it out.
怎樣？嗯-嗯。
That good? Uh-huh.
抱歉我遲到了。
我跟人大吵一架，
Sorry I'm late.
Al and I had a big fight.
然後又和好。兩次這樣子了。
And then we made up. Twice.
你是流行服飾顧問？
You're the fashion coordinator?
莉兒告訴我帶你買點東西打扮一下。
Lil told me to get you something
that would make the kiddies drool.
相信我，懷奧萊特。
Trust me, Violet.
看來我有個購物的習題了。
I have a serious shopping problem.
跨下...有拉鍊。
耶。
- It has a zipper... in the crotch.
- Yeah.
誰會在外面穿這個？
Who'd wear that in public?
事實上，我有一件藍色的。
- Actually, I have it in blue.
-// You're unbelievable//
// Oh//
// You burden me
with your problems//
//By telling me more than mine//
//I'm always so concerned//
// With the way you say
you always have to stop//
// To think of us being one//
//Is more than I ever know//
// The things you say//
// You're unbelievable//
// Oh//
原諒我，爸，因為我的罪過。
Forgive me, Father, for I have sinned.
//Seemingly last less
Don't mean you can ask us//
////[Continues]
[Hooting, Cheering]
// You're unbelievable, oh//
我在這！耶！寶貝！
Here I am! Yeah, baby!
// You're unbelievable////
來吧！擊掌吧！
Come on! Knock it--
Hey! Knock it off!.
莉兒！冰！
Lil! The ice!
喜歡這樣嗎？哈
How do you like that, huh?
// There's every good reason////
我不知道你們怎麼辦到的，
我再也喝不了了。
I don't know how you guys do it.
I can't have another drink.
下次再有人請你喝--我來，寶貝。
Next time that guy buys you a shot--
That's on me, honey.
用啤酒解決。
Chase it with a beer.
我不了解。
我並沒有喝下去。
- I don't get it.
- I don't swallow it.
我只是又把它吐回啤酒瓶裡。
只是他們都不知道。
I just spit the shot back into the beer bottle.
They'll never know.
試看看吧。
You try it.
嘿，要好好看牢你的瓶子。
Hey,just keep an eye on your spittoon bottle.
有一次瑞秋替勞服務時出了意外。
有很多精彩鏡頭。
Once Rachel served hers to Lou by accident.
Huge drama.
康妮，我想我開始愛上你了。
Cammie, I think I just fell in love with you.
喔，懷奧萊特！我不是女同性戀，
Oh, Violet! I'm not a lesbian.
只不過腦子想想罷了，但絕不會去做。
I've played in the minors, but never went pro.
我--我不是那個意思。
你們在幹嘛啊？
- Th-That's not what I meant.
- What are you doing?
莉兒開始一直盯著你。來吧，
招呼這傢伙，讓你自己看起來很忙的樣子。
Lil's starin' straight at you.Come on.
Grab this guy. Make yourself look busy.
嗨，你看起來像是要來一份的樣子。
不，我還再等莉兒。
- Hi. You look like you could use a shot.
- No, I'm waiting on Lil.
抱歉，這裡是不能空佔著的。
如果你要坐在這的話，麻煩你點份飲料。
Sorry. It's a no parking zone.
If you wanna sit here, you gotta order a drink.
好吧，給我杯水。
好吧。
- Okay. Gimme a glass of water.
- Okay.
他要點杯水。
耶。
- He just ordered water.
- Yeah.
你知道該怎麼做的。
You know what to do.
嗯--
Um--
試音。嗯，嘿，你們大家，
這傢伙剛點了杯水。
Testing. Um, hey, everybody,
this guy just ordered water.
我們這吧有賣水嗎？
Do we serve water in our bar?
不要水！
[Everyone]
Hell, no!H20!
杰西！不要！
Jersey! No!
沒關係啦，莉兒！
沒有人在這吧點水的！
It's okay, Lil!
Nobody orders water in your bar!
他可以在這點任何他想要的東西。
他是個消防局的主管。
He can order whatever he wants.
He's the fire marshal.
嘿，麥克，真抱歉，她是新來的。
Hey, Mike, I'm so sorry.
She's new.
沒關係，我們到外面去吧。
I'm okay.
Let's step outside.
很高興認識你，杰西。
-//Party//
- Nice knowing you,Jersey.
來吧，大家！讓我聽見你們！
-// Getnaked////
- Come on, you guys! Let me hear you!
你還好吧？
You okay?
我像開玩笑的嗎？
我做不來。
Who am I kidding?
I can't do this.
你可以的。提起勁來，
Of course you can. Now cheer up,
因為外面有個可愛的傢伙在找你。
because there's a really cute guy at the bar
asking for you.
有人找我？
Somebody's asking for me?
他說他叫歐當奴先生。
He says his name is Mr. O'Donnell.
他很正點。
He's hot.
杰西，消防局主管威脅要關我的店，
Jersey. The fire marshal
threatened to shut me down.
他開了張250元的罰單。
莉兒，我真的很抱歉--
- He let me go with a $250 fine.
- Lil, I'm really sorry--
我們來個協議，你今晚替我賺回 250塊，
I'll make you a deal.
You figure out a way to make me 250 tonight,
明天我讓你回來。
I'll let you come back tomorrow.
太好了。
Great.
真是可愛天真啊。
So much for sweet and innocent.
給你找到了。
有人告訴我說來這女狼俱樂部看看。
- So, you found me.
- Some guys at work told me where I could look for Coyotes.
那麼，好好看吧，因為今晚是我最後一晚。
我想我被炒魷魚了。
Well, take a good look,because tonight's
my last night. I think I'm gonna get fired.
為什麼？
我要在 2 小時內賺 250 塊。
- Why?
- I have to make $250 in two hours.
這是完全不可能的。
It's completely impossible.
這裡有九塊，就從這開始吧。好嗎？
Here's nine dollars, just to get you started.
Okay?
我向來喜歡幫助需要幫助的朋友。
I always like to help a friend in need.
為什麼你要那樣看著我？
Why are you looking at me
like that?
凱文，我不要你的錢。
Kevin, I don't want your money.
好吧，嗯，大家聽好，女士們，
All right, uh, listen up. Ladies.
25 元起價...
The bidding will start at $25...
只有今晚。
for one night only.
你們會得到：純種的，有禮貌的，
You get this: pure bred, housebroken,
受過完全訓練的，狂嘯種男！
fully trained, yowling stud.
不要。
很便宜嘛。
- No way.
- That's pretty cheap.
懷奧萊特，你在幹嘛啊？
Violet, what are you doing?
你說你要幫我，
那麼...請轉身，先生，
You said you wanted to help,
so... turn around, sir,
讓大家看看吧。
let 'em take a look atya.
你為什麼對我做這？
Why are you doing this to me?
報仇時間，歐當奴先生。
It's payback time, Mr. O'Donnell.
現在，請轉身。
Now, turn around.
不，天啊，不，不要這樣。
No, God, no. Don't do this.
來吧，讓大家看你有什麼。
Go on, show 'em what you've got.
你確定？你確定要這麼做？
Are you in?
Do you wanna do this?
好吧，女士們，你們要給我什麼呢？
我出 20 塊。
- All right, ladies. What'll you give me?
- I've got twenty bucks.
[ Women Hooting ]
這邊出 25 塊。
I've got $25 right here.
出 35 塊吧！
Make it 35!
35 塊！
Thirty-five dollars!
40 塊！
你在幹嘛啊？
- Forty dollars!
- Get-- What are you doing?
來吧，女孩們，50 塊？
50 塊！
- Come on, girls, fifty?
- Fifty!
61 塊。
70 塊。
- Sixty-one dollars.
- I've got 70.
來吧，女孩們。75 塊？
75 塊！
- Come on, girls. Seventy-five?
- Seventy-five dollars!
80 塊！
來吧，女孩們。我聽到 85 塊？
Eighty dollars!
Come on, girls. Do I hear 85?
90 塊！95塊！
Ninety! Ninety-five dollars!
100 塊！
One hundred dollars!
//
就是這樣。
想跟媽媽回家嗎？
- That's it.
- You wanna come home with Mama?
哇！好咧！
[Bidder]
Whoa!Nice!
喔，耶！
Oh, yeah!
那是我的男孩。
That's my boy.
喔，耶，搖啊搖啊。
125 塊這邊！
- Oh, yeah. Shake it, shake it.
- $125 back here!
140 塊這邊！
來吧，來吧。
$140, right here.
Come on, come on.
//
我的天啊，女孩們，來吧。
150 塊你就可以看到屁股。
My goodness, girls, come on.
One fifty and you'll see the butt.
來吧，女孩們。
你們可以出更高的。
Come on, girls.
You can do better than this.
175 塊！
One seventy-five.
耶！
Yeah!
我們來吧。
200 塊！
There we go.
Two hundred dollars!
215 塊這邊！
250 塊。
- You've got 215 righ there!
- Two hundred and fifty dollars.
賣了，就 250 塊！
Sold, for $250!
不！
上來吧，寶貝，他是妳的了。
- No!
- Come on up, honey. He's yours.
可惡！
Damn you!
金髮的要出 275 塊。
The blonde would have gone 275.
跟我來吧。
Come with me.
為了這妳欠我一份大人情。
250 塊整。
You're gonna owe me big-time for this one.
That's 250 even.
嗯，嗯！喔。
Mmm. Mmm! Oh.
//I'm gonna see ya
I'm gonna meet ya, meetya
meetya one day//
/ Maybe next week
I'm gonna meetya /
//I'll meetya
I'll meetya//
最好賣完，女孩們。
[Lil]
Better close out, girls.
我可以問妳個問題嗎？
什麼？
- Can I ask you something?
- What?
那個--"Coyote Ugly"是什麼意思？
What-- What does""Coyote Ugly"" mean?
妳有在一夜情後醒來發現...
Did you ever wake up sober
after a one night stand...
一個男人躺在你手臂上，一副醜樣...
and the person you're next tois layin'on
your arm, and they're so ugly...
妳寧願咬斷自己手臂也不願冒險叫醒他們？
you'd rather chew off your arm
than risk wakin' them?
那就是這個意思。
走吧，小姐們。
- That's coyote ugly.
- Let's go, ladies.
嗯，為何妳要在經過那樣的事情後
替你的酒吧取這名子？
Well, why would you name
your bar after something like that?
嗯，因為"Cheers"這名子被人用了。
Well, because ""Cheers"" was taken.
計程車在前門外面。
Cabs are out front.
妳有錢了，杰西。
待會見。
- You're rich,Jersey.
- Seeya.
耶，晚安。
Yeah. Good night.
那贏得我的女人叫珊蒂羅斯菲德，
有三個小孩而且離了婚，
The woman who purchased me is named
Sandy Rosenfeld, a divorcee with three grown kids,
熱衷於走很長的路還有短毛獵犬
及義大利歌劇，
a passion for long walks and short-haired
hunting dogs and Italian opera.
她的前夫是個 C.P.A.，
她最愛的藝術家是梵谷，
Her ex-husbandis a C.P.A.
Her favorite artistis Van Gogh,
她在新年下的決心是減肥15磅--
及在音樂會中看到芭芭拉。
and her New Year's resolution is to lose
15 pounds--and to see Barbra in concert.
好吧，我是欠你。
Okay. I owe you.
你想幹嘛？
[ Chuckles ]
What do you want?
嗯，現在是凌晨三點半，
我要的是每個男人都想要的，
Well, it's 3:30 in the morning.
I want what every man wants.
早餐。
Breakfast.
就這樣？我跟你去吃早餐然後就扯平?
And that's it? I go to breakfast
with you, and we're even?
不，還沒有，因為我在酒吧裡跳舞，
No. We're not even close to even,
because I danced on a bar,
脫了我的襯衫，拉下褲子拉鍊，
I took off my shirt,
and I unzipped my pants.
好吧，來個協議吧。早餐加午餐。
Okay. Let's make a deal.
Breakfast and lunch.
早餐，午餐還有兩頓晚餐。
那是四次約會！
- Breakfast, lunch and two dinners.
- That's four dates!
是的，也許會成為我目前所有
第二長的關係。
Yep. Which would make it the second
longest relationship I've ever had.
上車吧。
- Getin the car.
- [ Laughs ]
喔，壞了今晚真討厭，不過看來我們
是沒法到任何地方了。
Oh, I hate to spoil your evening, but it looks like
we're not gonna go anywhere.
喔，天啊。
Oh, my God.
在紐約停車還真是困難啊。
It's hard to find parking in New York.
吃過土耳其的料理嗎？
就是這裡了。
You ever eaten Turkish?
This is the place.
嘿，你好嗎？
嗨，凱文。
- Hey. How you doin'?
- Hi, Kevin.
四份十足的？
沒問題。
- Four of the regular?
- Sure, yeah. Hey.
- Hey, Kevin. How are you, man?
- How you doin', man? Good.
這拿去吧，老兄。
從邁阿密飛來的。
Here it is, man.
Flown in from Miami.
檢查看看吧。
嘿，老兄，不必了，我相信你。
- Check out them erch an dise.
- Hey, man, no. I trust you.
好耶，好耶。
Allright, allright.
搞不懂你在幹嘛，但--
Look, uh, I don't know
what you're into, but--
神奇的蜘蛛人，
編號129，嶄新且保存良好的。
The Amazing Spider-Man,
number 129, mint condition.
值一千塊。
一本漫畫書。
- Worth a thousand bucks.
- A comic book.
不，他不只是一本漫畫書，
這是第一次公開發行的版本。
No, it's not just a comic book.
This is the first appearance of the Punisher.
這是漫畫書中的聖杯。
This is the holy grail of comic books.
你收集漫畫書。真可愛。
耶。
- You collect comic books. That's so cute.
- Yeah.
這不可愛。
這是強壯且有男子氣概的。
It's not cute.
It's vety rugged and manly.
這是有一點不正常的，嗯？
我想這很可愛。
- It's just a bit kinky. Huh?
- I think it's sweet.
那麼，你常在你車子的引擎蓋上吃早餐嗎？
So, do you always eat breakfast
on the hood of your car?
我能說什麼？
我是個浪漫主義者。
What can I say?
I'm a romantic.
你認為這是浪漫？
You think this is romantic?
這個，也許你現在尚未感受到，
但是我想也許有一天...
Well, you may not be feeling it now,
but I think one day...
在某個舞台上唱著一首關於這個非常夜晚的歌。
嗯。
-you'll be on stage singing a song about this very night.
- Mmm.
""When We Were Downwind From a Trash Barge.""
耶，抓到主題了，
Yeah. Catchy title.
Hum a few bars.
抱歉讓你失望了，
我是個寫歌的，不是歌手。
Sorry to disappoint you,
but I'm a song writer, not a singer.
當我站上舞台時，我愣住了。
When I get on stage,
I freeze.
那如果自由世界被你歌聲征服了呢？
What if the fate of the free world
rested on your voice?
好吧，如果自由世界靠我的歌聲，
Okay. If the fate of the free
world depended on me singing,
也許吧。
maybe.
我只想要的是坐在一個黑暗的角落...
All I ever really wanted is to sit in the dark...
聽著某個人把我的歌唱的很棒。
and hear someone great singing my songs.
我想要當那種做音樂的人。
I wanna be the one who writes the music.
我還記得我媽第一次播放那首
"" Bridge Over Troubled Water""...
I remember the first time my mother played me
由"賽門與葛芬柯"唱的。
by Simon and Garfunkel.
我還完全記得當時她的穿著。
I remember exactly what she was wearing.
完全記得她頭髮的聞起來的味道，
當時我的感受。
I remember exactly how her hair smelled.
I remember exactly how I felt.
每當我聽到這首歌時，
And every time I hear that song,
我完全記得當時她的穿著...
I remember exactly
what she was wearing...
完全記得她頭髮的聞起來的味道，
and exactly how her hair smelled...
當時我的感受。
and exactly how I felt.
因為好歌是永遠的。
'Cause the great songs last forever.
那麼，問題是？
嗯...
- So, what's the problem?
- Well...
現在讓我的歌被人聽到的唯一辦法...
now they're telling me the only
way to get my songs heard...
就是我自己唱。
is to go out there and sing 'em myself.
那麼我們就按部就班的解決這問題吧。
So we're gonna have to try fix this
little problem straight away.
嗯，那你有什麼建議？
Hmm. And how do you propose
we do that?
嗯，有什麼地方可以讓你自在的唱歌？
Well, is there any place
you feel comfortable singing?
浴室。
我們就那開始吧。
- The shower.
- We'll start there.
我不管你要在浴室花多久時間，
I mean, I don't care how long it takes,
how many hours we have to spend in that shower.
走吧。
好吧，在那之前，
- Let's get to it.
- Okay. Before we hit the showers,
也許你可以告訴我些關於你自己的事情。
maybe you could tell me
a little something about yourself.
喔，真的？
你想知道啥？
Oh, really?
What do you wanna know?
你是從澳洲哪來的？
What part of Australia are you from?
很多地方，我家常搬來搬去，
I'm from all over.
My family moved around a lot.
那麼你家現在不住在紐約？
So the rest of your family
doesn't live in New York?
你常問有關這個很多問題嗎？
Do you always ask this many questions?
你常避開關於這方面的問題嗎？
Do you always dodge this many questions?
至少你可以告訴我你今晚在酒吧的
那誇張的動作在哪學的。
You can at least tell me where you go tall
the moves you pulled on the bar tonight.
嗯，如果我告訴你的話，我想我要宰了你。
Well, if I told you, I'd have to kill you.
那是獨創的。
喔。
- [ Scoffs ] That's original.
- Oh.
太陽要出來了，我們會遲到的。
The sun's coming up.
We're gonna be late.
遲到？去哪遲到啊？
Late? Late for what?
真不敢相信。
This is incredible.
看那條魚！
好啦，穿上這個，你會需要它的。
- Look at that fish!
- Allright. Put this on. You're gonna need it.
為什麼？你在說什麼啊？
Why? What are you talking about?
你要幫我卸下下一箱。
You're gonna help me
unload the next bin.
你在開玩笑吧？
沒有，沒那麼糟啦！懷奧萊特。
- You're joking, right?
- No. It's not that bad, Vi.
我常做這個。
你到底有多少個工作啊？
- I do it all the time.
- Exactly how many jobs do you have?
星期二到星期六，我在俱樂部做。
Tuesday through Saturday,
I'm at the club.
星期日跟星期一，我在廣場幫人停車。
Sunday and Monday
I park cars at the plaza.
我也當過電話市場員。
有沒有想換過 AT&T？
I've been a telemarketer.
Would you like to switch to AT&T?
也在皇后區送過電話簿。
And for six terrifying hours
I delivered phonebooks in Queens.
不要忘了你在魚堆裡的一堆事啊。
Don't forget your extensive work in fish.
這是個物價高的城市，這些人付現金當工資。
This is an expensive city, and these guys pay cash.
我才不管他們付什麼，
我可不想碰那些裝魚的大箱子。
I don't care if they pay in lobster.
I'm not sticking my hands in that fishy bin.
我本想分錢給你的說，
I was gonna split the money with you.
每人 100 塊。
100 塊？
-A hundredbucks apiece.
- A hundred bucks?
等等，為什麼你沒提這個？
謝啦，丹。
- Wait, wait. Why didn't you say so?
- Thanks, Dan.
你準備好了嗎？ 50 塊喔。
等等，不。
-You're not ready, are you? Fifty bucks.
-Wait. No.
25 塊，10塊，準備好了嗎？
好吧。嗯哼。
- Twenty-five, ten. Ready?
- Okay. Uh-huh.
喔！真噁心啊。
Ooh! That's disgusting.
嘿，你會傷它們感情的，好吧。
就堆在其他魚的上面。
Hey, you'll hurt their feelings. Okay.
Just on top of the other fish.
嗯，我知道我才認識你幾天，
但是有些事情是我必須告訴你的。
So, I know I just met you a few days ago.
There's something I have to tell you.
你聞起來真的很糟。
You smell really bad.
嗯，你也一樣。我本來想跟你吻別的，
但是，嗯，我想我也許會吐。
Well, so do you. I mean, I was gonna kiss
you good-bye, but, um, I thought I might gag.
你真是個令人著迷的傢伙。
You're a real charmer.
好吧，晚安。
Okay. Good night.
早安。
Good morning.
不要那樣子看我。
Don't look a tme like that.
花掉它吧！
Spend it.
你在這幹嘛啊？
關於那個吻我想我改變主意了。
- What are you doing here?
- I changed my mind about this kiss.
我想我們該試試。
I think we should give it a shot.
那麼，祝你有愉快的一天。
Well, have a nice day.
祝你有愉快的一天？
"" Have a nice day""?
對啊，我緊張，
不知道有什麼其他可以說的。
Yeah. I panicked.
I didn't know what else to say.
祝你有愉快的一天。
Have a nice day.
好的。這邊的退到線後面。退到線後面。
All right. Back of the line over here.
Back of the line.
耶！哇！
Yeah! Whoa!
[ Both Hooting ]
哇！
Whoa!
[ Shouting Continues ]
耶！我喜歡這個！
耶！
- Yeah, I like it!
- Yeah!
嘿，寶貝！
讓開，讓開！
- Hey, baby!
- Make a hole. Make a hole!
可惡，條子來了。
沒人進的來了，看看這個地方。
- Shit, the cops are here.
- Nobody else gets in here. Look at this place.
嘿，莉兒，我很抱歉。
這我們啥事都不能做，你客人太多了。
Hey, Lil. I'm sorry. There's nothing we can do here.
You're 50 people over max.
他們想叫我們關門。
They're trying to shutus down.
我們到外面談吧。
我來處理這個。
Let's go outside and talk.
I'll take care of it.
嘿！嘿！
Hey! Hey!
這個不是加油機，老兄！
- This is not a gas pump, son!
- [ Shouts ]
還沒輪到你！
Wait your turn!
[ Shouting, Arguing ]
嘿，不准拍照，老兄！
嗨，我是 The Voice 的記者。
- Hey, no pictures, man!
- Hey, I'm a reporter from The Voice.
耶！
Yeah!
哇！
Whoa!
你們在幹嘛？嘿！
What are you doing? Hey!
放我下來！嘿！
- Put me down!
- Hey!
放我下來！
康妮！
- Put me down!
- Cammie!
救命啊！
拜託！放她走！
- Help!
- Come on! Let her go!
瑞秋，救命啊！
Rachel, help!
來吧！
住手！
Come on!Break it up!
勞，瑞秋跟康妮呢？
我不知道！
- Lou, where's Rachel and Cammie?
- I don't know!
[ Shouting, Grunting ]
放我走！
Let me go!
[ Shouting, Grunting Continue ]
杰西，他們要把這地方拆了！
-////[Rock]
-Jersey, they're tearing this placea part!
瑞秋！瑞秋！
- Rachel! Rachel!
-// One way or another
I'm gonna findya//